SAGAR BETKAR

Mumbai, India (+91) 9702396398 | <u>sagarbetkar1994@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u> | <u>Website</u>

PROFILE DESCRIPTION

Full-Stack Developer with more than four years of experience developing responsive web applications, microservices & various integrations. A Can-do attitude, perseverance, and being a team player, gaining a little knowledge each day, always looking for a chance of self-improvement, and keeping an eye on what's next. Good understanding of JavaScript, React, Redux & Node.js. Most of my work so far has been written with Javascript, React, Redux, Mobx, Angular, Node.js, Express, MongoDB. *Open to relocation on a global level*.

SKILLS

Languages	HTML5,	CSS3,	JavaScript,	Typescript,	GraphQL,	, Sass, PHP.
Languages	1111112,	COO,	, Javasciipi,	iypcaciipt,	GrupriQL,	, Juss, I I II .

Libraries and Databases React, Redux, Mobx, Socket.io, Node.js, Ant design, MongoDB,

MySQL.

Frameworks Angular, Next.js, Nest.js, Express, React-Bootstrap, Bootstrap,

AngularJS, Slim.

Project Skills Agile Methodology, Collaboration, Communication, Pair Programming,

Time Management, Team player, Problem Solving, Git.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Knoxpo, Mumbai, India

March 2019 - Present

Full Stack Developer

- Build features, microservices and applications with a mobile responsive design.
- Converted wireframes and visual designs into working front-end code.
- Experience in an agile environment (Scrum, Kanban), PRs reviews, pair programming, working under pressure & tight timelines.
- Deployed web application using Docker(Kubernetes) on Google Cloud Platform.
- Experience with source control tools Git, Github, Gitlab.
- Technologies used so far:- React, Redux, Mobx, Typescript, GraphQL, Node.js, Express, Angular, MongoDB, Mongoose, Socket.io, Ant design, Next.js etc.

Freelancer, Mumbai, India

August 2018 - February 2019

Full Stack Developer

- Designing and developing APIs.
- Technologies such as HTML5, SCSS, Angular, Typescript, Node.js, MongoDB, Express (MEAN Stack) & deployed on AWS.
- Close collaboration with clients for a better workflow.

3Y Ventures LLP (tag8), Mumbai, India

January 2018 - August 2018

Software Developer

- Manage the IT development projects (Website, mobile app and web services) undertaken with IT partners.
- Maintain Server-side requirements & deployed web applications on AWS.
- Support internal development and enhancements project.
- Set up client jobs and support clients on project execution.
- Handle client's queries related to tag8 systems.
- Troubleshoot IT issues and resolve them.
- Support new IT/product development projects.
- Used technologies such as AngularJs, Bootstrap, PHP (Slim framework), SQL.

Stalkerscode Private Limited, Mumbai, India

August 2017 - December 2017

Web Developer

- Created responsive web pages as per visual designs by designers.
- Gained hands-on expertise in Bootstrap.
- Developed responsive websites using the technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap & PHP.

INTERNSHIPS

Software Developer internship at 3Y Ventures LLP (tag8) through Internshala Developed an in-house B2B web application for placing an order of companies products.
[January 2018 – March 2018]

EDUCATION

University of Mumbai, India

July 2012 - June 2017

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science.